<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sparks Blog</title>
    <description>Sparks is a project that will provide a rapid, secure and easy-to-use many-to-many conferencing tool based on WebRTC once it&#39;s finished :)</description>
    <link>http://northernlight.github.io/sparks/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://northernlight.github.io/sparks/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 20:28:03 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 20:28:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>TechDemo!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;First demo is up and running!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can announce very happily, that we managed to get our first little techdemo ready :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the latest git code you should now be abled to simulate a simple 1-to-1 session including session-generation, WebCam-access and video-stream capability.
From now on we will work on n-to-n communication and also on a nicer state handling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more #progress!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://northernlight.github.io/sparks/jekyll/2015/09/14/tec-demo/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://northernlight.github.io/sparks/jekyll/2015/09/14/tec-demo/</guid>
        
        <category>success</category>
        
        <category>techdemo</category>
        
        <category>progress</category>
        
        <category>WebRTC</category>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Sparks</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Sparks!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Sparks project is trying to realize and establish an easy and secure audio- and video-connection between serveral 
participants all over the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal is to provide a application - only used in the browser - that implements e.g. videochatrooms that can be easily 
set up by entering a username and generating a unique room-id afterwards. Once the meeting room is created, it should be
possible to invite and add friends or business partners to join the call without any further registration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would like to ensure a secure connection with using encrypted P2P-connections created with the WebRTC API.
Furthermore we will work on a traffic load-balancing algorithm to make sure every user can maintain a fluent stream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But for now, we have just set up this basic blog, where you will be abled to follow the project progress.
If you&amp;#39;re interested in our work, feel free to subscribe to our RSS-Feed :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://northernlight.github.io/sparks/jekyll/2015/09/08/welcome-to-sparks/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://northernlight.github.io/sparks/jekyll/2015/09/08/welcome-to-sparks/</guid>
        
        <category>welcome</category>
        
        <category>to</category>
        
        <category>sparks</category>
        
        <category>WebRTC</category>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
